# Caleb Wagner

# Software Developer

calebwagner5@gmail.com • 615-636-7127 • calebwagner.github.io/portfolio-website/

### CAREER SUMMARY

**Experience** 1+ year as Software Developer with a large company on the tech side of Healthcare

Languages Javascript, React, Ember, Vue, HTML, CSS, Python, Java, SQL

Tools Visual Studio Code, GitHub, Git, PostMan, Swagger, Intellij, Azure DevOps

Methodologies Scrum, Kanban, CI/CD, Pair Programming

**App Management** Experience with foundational and platform upgrades

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### HCA Healthcare - Digital Patient Experience

Nashville, TN

Application Engineer I

01/2022 - 08/2022

Technologies: React, Vue, Ember, Javascript, Typescript, CSS, HTML, Java, SpringBoot, MySQL, DB2

- Part of a 7 person developer team enhancing and supporting product serving over 5 million users.
- Released features and bug fixes as part of 2-week sprints, with a personal velocity of 4 items per sprint.
- Responsible for upgrading 2 new features and maintaining 10+ others features, with 2 legacy.

### Application Engineer Intern

10/2021 - 12/2021

- Paid internship turned into a permanent position.
- Enhanced and maintained static landing page for desktop and mobile desktop applications.
- Worked on tasks assigned by Sr. Team members such as bug fixes, issue resolution, and root cause analysis.

### **Projects**

# Where Was I | Front-End Application | Solo Project

Technologies: Javascript, React, JSX, CSS

- Built a productivity note-taking application as part of boot camp capstone.
- My goal for this application was to incorporate CRUD functionality and further my understanding of React.

#### uTeachiLearn | Full-Stack Application | Solo Project

Technologies: Javascript, React, Python, Django, SQL, JSX, Tailwind

- Built a social media type application that connects students to teachers as part of boot camp capstone.
- My goal for this project was to create a full-stack application with CRUD functionality.

### Rare | Full-Stack Application | Group Project

Technologies: Javascript, React, JSX, CSS, Python, Django, SQL

- Built a 'Medium' like application as part of a group project.
- Gained experience collaborating with other developers building a full-stack application.

### Education & Accreditations

#### Nashville Software School

04/2021 - 09/2021

- Focused on Full-Stack Development.
- Utilized Javascript, React, Python, Django, SQL, Postman

08/2018 - 05/2020

## University of Tennessee, Knoxville

BA Economics